Crystal Geyser is the only
major US spring water bottled
at the mountain source.
[ Air horn blows ]
[ Dagny's "Backbeat" plays ]
Meredith: There are moments
when all the stars align.
When everything seems
as it should be.
♪
♪ Right now ♪
Your life seems
to have sorted itself out.
♪ You got me feeling like
I can't believe I let you go ♪
It's not like
all our problems go away.
Oh, no.
What?
We fell asleep.
We fell asleep?
Yeah.
My kids will be up.
They'll see you.
Why is that
such a bad thing?
I've been over here
a lot lately.
And they've never seen you.
Do you think that's an accident?
What, so you don't want me
to meet them?
Not in my bed.
Okay, I understand.
Okay. [ Laughs ]
Not yet.
Just tell me where to go.
Down the stairs
and out through the back door.
Okay,
I'll be quiet as a mouse.
♪ If you really wanna dance
some more ♪
It's just that the problems
are suddenly manageable.
♪ We're
borderline wasting time ♪
♪ Pick it up and tell me ♪
You feel so good,
you wonder if it's real.
♪ That you love me
like you did before ♪
♪ I understand, understand ♪
♪ I been feeling it so long ♪
♪ I'm flying
when I'm in your arms ♪
[ Sighs ]
And if I've learned anything...
[ Knocking at door ]
♪ I'm burning up, burning up ♪
...I can tell you...it is.
♪ Feeling like a kid myself
again ♪
It's very real...
[ Music stops ]
...but it will not last.
Are you Major Owen Hunt?
I am.
Sir, I'm Major William Allen.
This is Chaplain Jane Roosevelt.
We're with
the Army Human Resource Command.
♪
Is this about my sister,
Megan?
Major, we have reason to believe
that...
[ Buzzing ]
[ Speaking distortedly ]
[ Breathing echoes ]
♪
[ Distorted speaking continues ]
[ Breathing echoes ]
♪
Captioning provided by
ABC Studios and ABC, Inc.
and brought to you by Ford.
We go further, so you can.
Richard: Just tell them
I'll need to push
my 3:00 lecture to 4:00.
Thank you.
Aren't you supposed to be
at counseling?
I went.
I went three times.
Mm.
I barfed up
all my childhood sadness.
I told them all my demons.
I participated.
I feel like
I got enough out of it.
Edwards...
What I did was wrong.
I know. I'm sorry.
But I don't think I should miss
out on another day of education
because I didn't get a stupid
piece of paper signed.
Ah, you feel calm?
You feel controlled?
Yes, yes.
How's your throwing arm?
Retired.
Give it to me.
[ Pen clicks ]
Now get back to work.
And if, uh, Dr. Minnick...
I will talk to Dr. Minnick.
You are
the One True King, sir.
Get out of here.
[ Laughs ]
♪
What do you mean,
you're there? Where?
I hired a guy. He gave me
his name and where he works.
Turned out he was scheduled
to do a minimally invasive
conference here in L.A.
So, you're there
and Jo's husband is there.
Yeah,
I'm looking right at him.
Alex!
What are you doing?
I don't know.
[ Sighs ] I don't know
if I'm gonna do anything.
Come home.
I can't yet.
I gotta go.
Do I need a badge
or something?
What do we have?
BP's 95 palp.
Somnolent, but responsive
to painful stimuli.
Stats are 92
with 100 percent oxygen.
On my count,
one, two, three.
It's an MVC?
Sort of.
Two people in one car drove off
a cliff on Admiral Way.
Do we have a name?
Haven't seen an ID yet.
They didn't find a purse?
They didn't even find
a blouse.
She came in
dressed like this.
Why are people driving around
with no clothes on?
Passenger's next door.
Maybe he knows.
Talk to me!
Male passenger, 30s,
unconscious
and intubated at the scene.
Vitals are stable.
Uh, large bruises,
right chest and abdomen.
Was he dressed?
Except for his pants.
So, these two
were not driving.
They were parking.
The theory
is they got overexcited
and popped the car
into gear.
Premature acceleration.
You know, it happens
to a lot of guys.
People need to get busy
where God intended --
parking lots,
where it's flat.
[ Both laugh ]
[ Buzzing ]
[ Distorted conversations ]
[ Elevator bell dings
distantly ]
[ Breathing echoes ]
[ Elevator door thuds open ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
♪
[ Breathing echoes ]
[ Heartbeat ]
[ Distorted conversations ]
♪
[ Speaking distortedly ]
[ Buzzing continues ]
He's got a head lac, and they
both have abdominal injuries.
Uh, Bailey's here,
and I paged Dr. Grey.
You can jump in
if you want,
but I think
we got it covered.
[ Buzzing continues ]
[ Speaking distortedly ]
[ Distorted voice ]
Okay.
[ Speaking distortedly ]
♪
Denise:
Somebody please help, please!
Please!
Please, someone help us!
My baby can't breathe!
Gary:
She's choking on something.
[ Buzzing continues ]
[ Sobs ]
[ Baby choking ]
02 and crike kit, please?
Is she dying?
[ Sniffles, crying ]
Mommy, is she dying?
Gary:
She's choking on something.
Okay.
Move. Move!
[ April
breathing quickly ]
Oh, my God!
Gary: Hey, stop!
[ Baby crying ]
-Oh!
-You're okay. You're okay.
How long
had she been choking?
I don't know --
a -- a few minutes -- five?
Page neuro.
The baby's brain may have been
deprived of oxygen for too long.
Next time,
call an ambulance.
What?
[ Crying continues ]
♪
We know how it feels to be
treated like a trophy.
Waxed and shined.
We have seen the glory come,
go, and come again.
But a Cadillac is no trophy.
What you see is our future,
And It will inspire every car
that follows.
♪
Starting Thursday at Kohl's
save on gifts for mom
and get Kohl's Cash for you!
Pick out a diamond
ring for just $79.99
and get $10 Kohl's Cash!
A cookware set
and get $20 Kohl's Cash!
Or the Fitbit Charge 2
and you'll get $30 Kohl's Cash!
Kohl's.
There's nothing more
important to me
than my vacation.
So when I need to
book a hotel room,
I want someone
that makes it easy
to find what I want.
Booking.com gets it.
They offer free cancellation,
in case I decide to go from
kid-friendly to kid-free.
Now I can start relaxing
even before the vacation begins.
Your vacation is very important.
That's why Booking.com
makes finding
the right hotel for
the right price easy.
Visit Booking.com now
to find out why
we're Booking.yeah
Hey Allergy Muddlers
Are you one sneeze away from
being voted out of the carpool?
Try ZYRTEC®
It's starts working hard at hour
one
And works twice as hard when you
take it again the next day.
Stk with ZYRTEC® and Muddle No
More®.
Know what makes retirement
less scary?
("Mambo No. 5" playing)
Getting a check every month.
With an income annuity
from New York Life,
you pay some money up front
and then get checks
for the rest of your life.
One, two, three, four,
five checks.
Be good at life.
New York Life.
Introducing McDonald's new
Signature Crafted Recipes.
Like the Maple Bacon Dijon
burger.
Applewood smoked bacon with
sweet maple seasoning.
Grilled onions.
And a creamy Dijon sauce with a
hint of honey.
On chicken or seared beef.
When I'm with you...
...The rest of the world...
...Fades away.
So I got you something...
...That stands out...
...As beautifully as you do...
Jared has more
exclusive LeVian pieces
than any other jewelry
store in the world.
That's why he went to Jared.
Lower extremity deformity
with a large hematoma.
Can't find a pedal pulse.
Trauma panel,
type and cross her eight.
I hope the sex was good.
Is sex in a car
ever that good?
All those windows...
[ Groaning ]
Hey. Miss.
Hey, you're okay.
You're at Grey-Sloan Memorial.
I do need you to keep still
though, okay?
Abdomen's very distended.
Bring me the ultrasound now.
Is he alive?
Can you tell us your name?
Alison.
Please,
is he -- he alive?
[ Coughing ]
Oh, oh!
-Rapid intubation.
-Oh, okay. Okay. Okay.
I need 7-O ET tube.
She has a lot of blood
in her abdomen.
[ Coughing ]
Alison, we're gonna take you
up to the O.R. now.
[ Monitor beeping rapidly ]
Pressure's dropped,
70 over 40!
She's bleeding out.
Hang blood on the infuser
and prep her for REBOA catheter.
No hemotympanum.
Battle sign
behind the right ear.
He needs a head CT.
I need you to explain
why you're here, Edwards.
Yeah, I got a six-centimeter
oozing forehead lac here.
I'm gonna need a suture tray
when you're done.
You assigned counseling.
I've been counseled.
Andrew: Lactate 2.1,
crit is 42,
labs are good.
I'm seeing fluid
in Morrison's pouch.
You went to counseling
for a minute.
My paper's been signed
by Dr. Webber.
Oh, of course he did.
We need to clear him
for a liver lac.
And until we rule that out,
DeLuca,
we need to keep him
on close observation.
No, DeLuca.
That's all you, Edwards.
No, I can't.
I'm on neuro.
You were. And now,
you're on babysitting duty.
[ Scoffs ] I'm sorry, two
horndogs crash their sexmobile,
and I don't get a surgery
out of it?
Well, lucky for you.
You can sew up my head lac.
[ Tool clatters ]
[ Sighs ]
I should've just gone
to the stupid counseling.
Damn right you should have.
Page me
when you get the scans.
[ Monitor beeping ]
♪
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, hey.
[ Laughs ]
What does that do?
This is epinephrine.
It's for cardiac arrest.
Do you know what that is?
Okay. So, we'll just put that
back there
and find out
who you belong to.
Where are your parents?
Over here.
♪
She's breathing fine.
I think you can start
to feed her.
Yeah, what about
her -- her brain?
The other doctor said
the oxygen, uh...
I think I found
something of yours.
Oh, my God.
Oh my gosh,
where have you been?
Please keep a close eye on her.
It's very busy in here today.
Yeah, I got it.
Gary, put the phone down.
Well, I'm texting Karen.
Why are texting the nanny?
She's off this week.
Yeah, but there's, like,
a lot going on, right?
So, maybe she could just...
Erin, you have to stay
with Daddy, okay?
Her neurological exam
looks fine.
Her reflexes are good.
She's alert.
I'd like to keep her here
for a few hours for observation
as a precaution,
all right?
Yeah, okay.
Um, the other doctor...
[ Baby crying ]
...the one who, um,
pounded on her --
what's his name?
Was that Dr. Hunt?
Yes.
Uh, we'd like to talk to him
if we could.
I'll, uh,
tell him to come by.
What was that about?
I don't know.
♪
[ Sighs ]
Hey. What are you doing?
Okay, uh...
Did you treat a choking baby
this morning?
What,
are we not speaking now?
Yes! Why?
Uh, baby's in the PICU
for observation.
She looks good, but the parents
want to speak to you.
Why?
I don't know.
I don't know if they're upset
or if they just...
Upset
because I saved their baby?
Look,
I am just the messenger.
They want to speak to you.
[ Sighs ]
I'll talk to them.
Fine.
♪
[ Sighs ]
[ Mid-tempo music plays ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
It's okay.
I'll see you inside.
All right.
♪
Sorry to bug you.
Are --
Are you Paul Stadler?
Hi. Do I know you?
No, but I know you.
I couldn't put down
your paper
on new approaches to antibiotic
resistance to pathogens.
Ah, yes.
Thanks. Uh, that was fun.
It was part of
a whole WHO thing.
Listen, I am this close
to a grant for IBS research,
and your stuff...
I'm sorry.
I'm Alex.
Stevens.
Uh, can I buy you a drink?
[ Laughs ]
Absolutely.
♪ Dynamite ♪
[ Bottles clink ]
♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ I think you dynamite ♪
♪ Oh ♪
[ Distorted laughing ]
♪ And that's all right ♪
♪ She kind of prehistoric ♪
[ Cellphone ringing ]
God, stop calling!
Ugh!
I told my girlfriend that,
"I will see you on Monday,"
but every 20 minutes, she's
like, "What are you doing?"
[ Both laugh ]
Out of town
means out of town, bitch!
Paul.
Alex.
This is from your wife.
What?
[ Ringing continues ]
[ Both grunting ]
♪ Hunh ♪
♪ Ha ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪
[ Sirens wailing ]
[ Door buzzes ]
[ Door clangs shut,
lock engages ]
♪
[ Indistinct conversations ]
We, the entertainment-loving
people,
want all our rooms to be TV
rooms.
Because those are the best
Because they have TVs in them.
And, when we're not in those
rooms,
we want our shows to go with us.
Anywhere?
You got that right, kid show
thing.
Get a DIRECTV all-included
package for 4 rooms.
Only $25 a month, price
guaranteed for 2 years.
Available for AT&T Unlimited
Plus customers.
Hi guys. It's great to be here.
In the desert.
At the mall.
On the mountain.
At school.
At the beach.
In the Big Easy.
Yeah.
Today I want to show you guys
the next-gen Chevy Equinox.
What do you think?
That's pretty.
Pretty sexy.
It's all-wheel drive.
Look at that.
It looks aggressive.
But not overbearing.
It's not too big.
Not too small.
It looks like it can go
off-roading.
But at the same time,
it looks like a car you can
take to a nice event.
You can dress it up
or dress it down.
Seems like the perfect car
for anybody.
I would take it anywhere.
I want one.
I love it.
She's a bad mama jama.
Chevy stepped their game up.
Come.
Explore a place where you can
fly on the back of a banshee.
Walk under floating mountains.
And navigate a mystical river.
Welcome to a
world - beyond belief.
Pandora - The World of Avatar.
Only at the Walt Disney
World Resort.
It's the biggest news ever
at Olive Garden
Introducing new
Giant Stuffed Pastas
starting at $12.99.
Pastas so big
you could share them,
but so delicious,
you won't want to.
Giant Stuffed Pastas.
For a limited time
at Olive Garden.
WELCOME TO MAXX YOU.
YOU ARE WHIMSICAL, VIBRANT,
STATEMENT MAKING.
WE SEE WHAT MAKES YOU UNIQUE.
SO WE HAVE SOMETHING
FOR EVERYONE,
AT A PRICE THAT'S
JUST RIGHT FOR YOU.
MAXX YOU. MAXX LIFE.
T.J.MAXX
[ Air rushing ]
[ Monitor beeping ]
You doing a single
interrupted suture layer, then?
No,
running a subcuticular.
Oh, even better.
Not conscious yet?
No. The girlfriend?
Still in the O.R.
His head CT is clear.
He has a grade-three liver lac.
Dr. Grey wants serial abdominal
exams and six-hour crits.
[ Monitor beeping rapidly ]
Oh, all right, sir.
Hold on. Hold on.
All right, I'm gonna get this
out of your throat, okay?
One second,
I'm gonna count to three
and
you're gonna blow it out.
One, two, and three.
[ Coughing ]
There you go. Great job.
Okay.
[ Coughing ]
Get you sat up.
Clear that airway.
What's happening?
Okay.
What are you doing?
Sir, you are in the hospital,
okay?
You had an accident.
Let's get started
with your name.
[ Gasping ]
What's your name?
Keith.
Okay.
Keith, Keith,
you're safe, okay?
We have Alison here, too.
Alison?
Mm-hmm.
She's here?
I-Is she all right?
Did you talk to her?
She was unconscious
when she came in.
Alison has pretty severe
internal injuries.
We've got her in surgery
right now.
Alison's in surgery?
Okay. Uh, uh,
w-when will she be out?
Oh, well,
that's hard to tell.
I have to go.
No no, settle down.
Settle down.
I have to go see her!
You need to stay in bed.
You're not going anywhere,
hold on.
Hold on. You need
to lie in bed, okay?
You have an injury
to your liver.
If you move,
it can make it much worse.
I have to...
Look, we are gonna make sure
to let you know how she is
as soon as she's out,
okay?
Okay.
Right now,
I need you to relax.
Okay.
Okay?
Thank you.
Thanks.
Great.
All right.
You're right.
It perfed the esophagus.
So, do you need
to open him up?
No, I think we should wait a day
and keep him on TPN.
[ Switches clicking ]
I know this girl.
She's trouble.
Hey, Erin.
Whatcha doing?
What does this do?
This...
does that.
Whoa.
Is that his ribs?
Mm-hmm, it's his ribs.
What's that?
That little thing
is a bullet.
Nuh-uh.
Uh-huh.
It broke his rib!
She's better at this
than you.
[ Laughs ]
Did he die?
No, no, no.
I mean, it hurt a bunch,
but I think he'll be all right.
My dumb baby sister almost died.
She choked.
And where are your parents?
Are they in the E.R.?
In the ICU.
I saw a man
with only one ear.
Whoa, really?
Well, I'd like to see that.
Would you like to see that?
Sure.
Yeah, maybe you could show us
the one-eared man
on the way back to your folks.
What do you say?
Yeah, come on.
[ Chuckling ]
Yeah? Okay.
Okay.
Is this him? Sir?
Uh, we think
this might belong to you.
I think we found you
a radiologist in training.
Gary: Yeah, thanks.
You're welcome.
Sorry about that.
No, no.
Thank you.
No worries.
That poor bloke
is losing his mind.
Yeah, some people
just need a nanny.
[ Pen clicks ]
So, do you want to, um,
come over for dinner tonight?
What about the kids?
With the kids.
You seem to like kids.
They seem to like you.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure. I mean,
maybe I could bring something.
Then you wouldn't
have to cook.
That's okay.
I'll make something they like.
After they go to bed,
you can...
stay.
Not all night,
just...for a while.
Sounds good.
Edwards, I assume
your patient's awake and stable
if you felt comfortable
leaving him.
Alert and oriented
times three.
Lacs are repaired.
Vitals are stable.
He's looking for an update
on his girlfriend.
Oh, hey,
is she awake?
Not yet.
How is her boyfriend, husband,
driving instructor?
Definitely not husband.
Dr. Pierce
repaired an aortic injury,
but she's not
out of anesthesia yet.
-Okay.
-Why not husband?
'Cause car sex
is only for when it's new.
Or it could be cheating.
Or why do it?
Someone
is always uncomfortable
with the gearshifts
and the consoles.
And just limbs,
everywhere.
You people need
bigger cars.
Keith was asking about her
as soon as he woke up.
Keith?
Yeah, the copilot.
Ah.
She did the same thing.
-She asked about him first, too.
-Hmm.
[ Clicks tongue ]
They're in love.
That figures.
"That figures"?
What do you mean?
Well,
two people who are in love
would want to go to a beautiful
place to share their love.
It figures that
they would wind up bleeding
in the bottom of a canyon.
Wow.
That's so cynical.
That's what happened!
Keith wants to be here
when she wakes up, okay?
But Grey wants him immobile
for 24 hours.
Guys, maybe it wasn't love,
all right?
Woman: Dr. Avery.
It's not romance
we're talking about here.
It was emergency sex,
and they were
just too damn horny
to remember
the parking brake.
That's super cynical.
What is wrong
with you people?
-Seriously.
-Wow.
You should let him come see her.
You should figure it out.
Why? Because Prince Charming's
kiss is gonna wake her up?
Prince Charming
has a grade-three liver lac
that could kill him
if he moves.
-Cynic!
That's not -- whatever.
Amelia.
Okay, so this is fun.
Owen is giving me
the silent treatment now.
No. Not you, me.
I need your help.
What?
I invited him over tonight.
Nathan?
To meet the kids.
Wow.
I know. I feel...
Nervous.
...nauseous.
I feel really sick.
Because you think
the kids will like him,
and then it'll fall apart
and he'll be gone
and the kids will be sad.
No, it's not that.
It's that.
I know this because I'm
the queen of thinking this way.
I always think
everybody's gonna die.
Yeah, but you're crazy.
I'm just...sick.
Derek is dead.
Maggie is fine.
There is nothing in your way
but you.
Let yourself have this.
Look at you
being the sane one.
Moments.
I have moments.
[ Woman speaking indistinctly
on PA ]
Dr. Hunt?
Yes. You asked to see me?
Yes.
[ Voice breaking ]
Um, this morning...
This morning...
[Crying]
...you saved her.
You saved our baby girl.
I never could have done
what you did.
[ Buzzing ]
[ Speaking distortedly ]
[ Breathing echoing ]
♪
[ Distorted voice ]
Stop it.
We thought we lost her,
but you brought her back
to us.
Stop it!
♪
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Sighs ]
Two soldiers
came to the house today.
They said they found her.
They said they found Megan.
Owen, I'm so sorry.
♪
[ Breathing deeply ]
At least you know.
Maybe
you can find some peace.
They said
that she's alive.
♪
♪ Hit it! ♪
♪ Now look what you made me do ♪
♪ You and me baby it takes two ♪
♪ Bringing new moves
to the old school ♪
♪ Time for the whole
world to enjoy the view ♪
♪ We can go left
They can go right ♪
♪ Save me a dance for
the end of the night ♪
♪ When I'm with
you it's a party ♪
♪ Don't care where we're going ♪
♪ 1, 2, 3 get loose now! ♪
♪ It takes two to
make a thing go right ♪
make it out of sight. ♪
♪I don't care about the funny
way you wear your hair♪
♪Someday you'll let me put my
comb up there♪
♪'Til then you're beautiful and
I just stare♪
Happy birthday.
I love it.
I am groot.
Yes, let's get tattoos. Perfect.
I am groot!
Someone's after you?
♪
I am groot!
I see it.
Yes!
So, uh...  Shhh...
Be the guardian of your galaxy
in the all-new Ford EcoSport.
Only in theaters May 5th.
♪
Where did we find the
inspiration for our new flavors?
It walked right in the door.
Introducing new Signature
Crafted Recipes.
Pico Guacamole.
Sweet Barbecue Bacon.
Maple Bacon Dijon.
Get a free medium Fries and soft
drink in the McDonald's App with
purchase of any Signature
Crafted Recipe sandwich.
You bring your flavor to the
world.
We bring ours to you.
Wish your skin
could bounce
back like it
used to?
Neutrogena Hydro
Boost Water Gel.
With hyaluronic acid
it plumps
skin cells with
intense hydration
and locks it in.
For supple,
hydrated skin.
Hydro Boost.
From Neutrogena
Allergies with nasal congestion?
Find fast relief
behind the counter
with Claritin-D.
[ upbeat music ]
Strut past that aisle
for the allergy relief
that starts working in
as little as 30 minutes
and contains the best
oral decongestant.
Live Claritin Clear,
with Claritin-D.
[Mom] Now that the kids have
flown the coop,
this place is too big.
[Dad] We raised them from eggs.
[Brad] Try Apartments-dot-com.
It's easy to downsize. Oh, how
about Florida?
[Dad] The kids will love it!
[Brad] Change your apartment.
Change the world.
I lost my sight
when I was 14 years old.
So I really navigate the world
by touch.
When Dove asked me to try out
this body wash...
I was excited that it was foam.
It was so light and soft...
Not sticky.
It's light.
It's different.
It's foam.
[ Wind rushing ]
They said they found her
in a basement
in a rebel-held
neighborhood.
There was a raid,
and they just left her there.
She was there for, uh...
Where is she now?
[ Sighs ] Germany.
Army Hospital.
Did you talk to her?
How was she?
When is she getting here?
I haven't...
No, I haven't.
Oh, my God, Evelyn.
What did your mother say?
H-Have you told her?
How do we -- How do we even know
that it's her?
What if it's not?
What if they --
What if they got it wrong?
I mean...
Owen.
They might have.
This might not be true!
-Okay.
-It might not be true.
Well...
let's find out.
Let's find out for sure.
Okay.
[ Horns honk ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
♪
Dr. Stadler's work
combined the worlds of fiber
optics and abdominal surgery...
♪ Word around town
and the whispers loud ♪
...forging the way
for an almost new specialty.
He started his research...
♪ The lights all show,
nobody makes a sound ♪
...when he was still a student
at Johns Hopkins,
showing an early interest
in...
♪ From the rooftops,
hear 'em callin' out my name ♪
[ Sighs ]
Good luck out there.
Yeah. Thanks.
♪ Sideways talking
never to my face ♪
You nervous?
No, I'm good.
I'm just about to make a speech.
[ Clears throat ]
I'm a friend of Brooke's.
♪ You don't want to be
the last to know ♪
Your wife, Brooke Stadler.
The one who left you.
Yeah, how's she doing?
Where is she now?
You don't get to know that.
You don't get to think about her
ever again.
And if you come near her,
I will find you
and I will kill you.
♪ Can't say
I never told you so ♪
You understand?
♪ Whoo, ooh, whoa, ooh ♪
Who are you?
Doesn't matter.
...Paul Stadler.
[ Applause ]
I know your name.
I know who you are.
And I'm watching you.
Dr. Paul Stadler.
Good luck.
♪ Can't say
I never told you so ♪
♪ Whoo, ooh, whoa, ooh ♪
[ Applause continues ]
♪ Remember my name,
remember my name ♪
♪ Whoo, ooh, whoa, ooh ♪
Hey, Jo, it's me.
[ Jo grunting ]
[ Door scrapes open ]
♪ Remember my name ♪
[ Jo choking ]
[ Grunts ]
Hey, Alex.
[ Thuds ]
[ Sniffles ]
Found her.
Thanks.
♪ You don't want to be
the last to know ♪
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Monitor beeping ]
Whoa.
Whoa, no!
[ Grunting ]
No, no, no, no.
What did I tell you?
I have to go.
Lie down. Lie down.
You're not supposed to move
for 24 hours.
Your liver
could start bleeding again.
You could bleed out.
No. Let me go, okay?
I can't.
I was the last face
she looked at.
And now she's gonna wake up
in a hospital
with a tube in her throat
and no idea how she got here,
and surrounded by strangers
and probably hurting like hell.
She's gonna be so scared.
You -- You don't know
how that feels.
Yeah, I do, actually.
I do.
Then let me be there
for her.
Let me be there
when she wakes up.
I-If she can just see me first,
she'll know she's okay.
S-She'll know,
a-and she won't be so scared.
Please?
Let me do that for her.
Help me.
Please.
Amelia: Nein,
ich versuche jetzt den status
den patienten zu finden.
Danke.
Yes, I'm calling on behalf
of Major Owen Hunt.
I'm looking for a patient.
Ask for Teddy Altman.
What?
Ask to talk to Dr. Altman.
Is there a Dr. Altman
there?
Yes, I'll hold.
You speak German.
Hey, Dr. Altman.
This is Amelia Shepherd
from Grey-Sloan Memorial.
I, uh --
I work with Owen Hunt.
Yes.
No.
One sec.
I'm sorry.
He won't --
Yeah, I'm -- I'm --
I'm calling about his sister.
Okay.
Uh, we just need
to confirm...
Right.
No, uh,
could we transfer her here
as soon as she touches down?
Yes, transfer to Grey-Sloan.
Thank you so much.
She said
she tried to call you.
Megan is being transferred
from Landstuhl now.
She will land at Madigan.
[ Scoffs ]
And then,
we'll bring her here.
We -- We don't even know
if it's her.
Owen, Teddy knows her.
Teddy saw her.
♪
[ Sniffling ]
I called Merritt Campbell.
She's the best PTSD expert
there is right now.
She'll be here
in the morning.
Yeah, well, let's just wait
and see how Megan is...
Okay.
But I meant for you.
For you, too.
♪
[ Chuckles ] I got married
right over there.
And I got divorced.
Then, I got married again.
[ Chuckles ]
Then I went on
with my life.
And I left Megan
in a hole in the ground
for almost 10 years.
Weeks would go by, and I...
didn't give her a thought.
I couldn't spare her
a thought
when she was being held
and tortured...
...and I don't know what.
♪
I stopped looking.
[ Crying ] I gave up.
I gave up on her.
I gave up.
[ Crying ]
♪
[ Elevator bell dings ]
[ Elevator door opens ]
[ Button clicks ]
So, Alison's waking up?
Oh, you're not cynical.
No, you're the one
that's cynical.
Maybe they were in love,
or maybe they were just horny.
It doesn't matter.
Okay.
We all love,
and we all get horny,
and we all get hurt,
and then we come through
the other side.
And we get to help them
do that.
We get to help them
love again.
Or screw again.
Either way. Win-win.
But I-I think they're in love.
I choose love.
Yeah.
What do we have to be cynical
about? Is my point.
Oh, that --
that's your point.
Got it.
Shut up.
[ Elevator bell dings,
doors open ]
♪
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Elevator bell dings ]
Is she waking up?
Yes, starting to.
Avery, you need something?
Jackson:
No, just curious.
Okay. Alison.
[ Groans ]
Alison. You with us?
What happened?
You were in an accident.
Is he dead?
Did I kill him?
Oh. No, no, no, it's okay.
You didn't do anything.
Please tell me
I killed him!
What did you say?
There was a man in my car.
Y-Yes. Yes, he's here.
We have him.
No. He -- He got into my car,
and he put a knife to my throat!
[ Sniffles ]
He made me drive to the woods.
He was trying to rape me.
And I thought, "No.
No. I'm not letting you
do this.
I'm not gonna let you do this,
not even if it kills me."
A-And I hit the gas.
Please t-tell me he's dead.
Call security.
Stephanie's with him.
♪
I am breaking the rules
for you.
So be very still, okay?
Thank you so much.
You are a lifesaver.
All right.
Let's get you out of here.
♪
How's it going?
Oh, it's going good.
Yeah, it's going good.
This is uh, this is my jam.
Yeah?
Yeah, it's going good.
This is uh, this is my jam.
What is that?
What?
The moment you realize the
gardening gene
skipped a generation.
At Lowe's, our grow together
planting system
takes the guess work out of
creating a beautiful yard.
All projects have a
starting point.
Start with Lowe's.
Hey, it looks good huh?
Not bad.
Now get 2 select hanging baskets
or planters for only $10
at the Lowe's
"Outdoor Entertaining Event."
♪
If you want to be
a world traveler, start by...
Ooh, is that a Galaxy S8?
Handsome screen.
Well, pack that...
...oop, oh OK,
we're moving fast.
You'll need a tour guide.
Apparently not.
Don't forget a big camera.
Or that phone will work.
Traveling by yourself
can be lonely.
And...
you've already made friends.
♪
OK, I guess you have the
world traveler thing covered.
♪
Right now at Kohl's
get 25% off Nike for mom.
That's 25% off select Nike
shoes, apparel and accessories
just in time for Mother's Day!
And, everyone gets
Kohl's Cash!
Earn it on everything!
Spend it on anything!
Right now at Kohl's.
[ Horn honks ]
Oh! [ Panting ]
[ Taxi door opens ]
Paul: Ah.
Oh, sorry. I tho--
I thought this was mine.
Um, you going to the airport?
You wanna split it?
[ Horn honks ]
No, I'll --
I'll let you have this one.
I'll get the next one.
Thanks, man.
[ Sighs ]
[ Taxi door closes ]
Airport, please.
♪
[ Elevator bell dings ]
ICU is reserved for,
uh, family only,
so I'm gonna fudge it.
Just follow my lead, okay?
[ Men panting ]
[ Police radio chatter ]
Brody, Brody, Brody.
What's going on?
Someone was assaulted.
What?
Yeah, I heard
a patient got raped.
They're looking
for the guy.
Hey, hey. No, no!
Don't get up. Don't get up.
[ Grunting ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Breathing quickly ]
Now, you're gonna show me
the way out of here.
Okay?
♪
[ Lock disengages ]
Okay, backpacks upstairs.
Let's get you guys changed.
Mommy has a friend coming over
for dinner.
Zola: Is it Owen?
No, it's someone
you haven't met.
Then why is Owen here?
I don't--
What's going on?
Why don't you get the kids
squared away
and we'll talk upstairs?
Okay. All right.
Let's go, guys. Come on.
♪
This guy's been
an absolute train wreck...
He -- He said...
I said some place
where people don't go,
like a service elevator.
I know. I know.
Are you screwing with me?
No.
'Cause if you are...
We just -- We just have to
get past him, okay?
Then we're fine.
And I said, "I don't know
how he could have broken it
playing Ping-Pong,"
[Chuckling] but, you know...
Look, just give him a script
for Keflex and send him home.
Woman: You got it.
Thanks, Dr. Warren.
Hey.
Um, y-you need a hand?
No, no.
We're fine. We're good.
Liver lac.
Taking him for a test drive.
Really?
Yeah, Minnick's orders.
All right.
[ Chuckles ]
All right,
where are we going?
Here.
[ Beeps ]
Aah!
♪
You think you're funny,
huh?
No, this goes right down
to the loading dock.
You think it'll be funny
when I cut your throat?
It's either this, or...
You told me I can't walk,
and now you're sending me
down the stairs?
You're trying to kill me!
It's either this
or the elevator with the police.
It's just this -- this is --
this is what you want.
Here.
Let me give you the card.
No!
No, no.
No, you're not gonna run
and tell them where I am.
You're gonna help me
down the stairs, all right?
Move.
[ Breathes sharply ]
I want someone with that woman
every second.
I want two officers
on this door.
Patient's gone. So is Edwards.
I can't find her anywhere.
She's not responding
to any texts.
Call a Code Orange.
Lock this place down.
♪
Keith: [ Grunting ]
Stephanie:
[ Whispering indistinctly ]
Oh, will you quit
that praying?!
I'm not praying.
Then what
do you keep saying?
I'm saying, "Please bleed out.
Please bleed out."
Yeah, I guess
I kinda am praying.
Shut up.
Aah!
I said don't try anything.
[ Breathing heavily ]
See?
See what happens?
If you...
[ Door opens ]
[ Door closes ]
[ Gasping ]
In here.
♪
[ Sniffles ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Erin: Hi.
[ Gasps ] What the hell?
You need to go.
You need to go out that door --
okay? -- right now.
It won't open again.
[ Whispering ]
Shut up.
[ Sniffles ]
Hey, sweetie.
What's your name?
Don't --
Erin.
Erin,
where are your folks at?
In the ICU with my baby sister
who choked.
You need to go, okay?
Wait.
And I'll let you out, okay?
Hold on!
[ Gasps ]
It's all right,
sweetheart.
Don't. Don't.
I'm just gonna let her out,
and then you and I can keep
going where we're going, okay?
No. She'll tell them
what she saw.
She doesn't know
I want my mom.
Okay?
Then we'll just go.
We'll go.
Leave her locked in here,
and we'll go down the stairs.
And by the time they find her,
we will be long gone, okay?
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
[ Beeping ]
No.
No, no!
Open it!
I can't. I can't.
I can't!
It's locked.
We're in lockdown.
Why?
Because a rapist
is in the hospital.
What,
we're trapped in here?
We're trapped in here.
♪
Hi Guys. It's great to be here.
In the desert. At the mall.
On the mountain. At school.
At the beach.
In the Big Easy.
Various: Yeah. Yeah.
Today I want to show you guys
the next-gen Chevy Equinox.
What do you think?
Woman:
That's pretty.
Woman 2:
Pretty sexy.
It's all-wheel drive.
Look at that.
Man:
It looks aggressive.
Woman 3:
But not overbearing.
It's not too big.
Not too small.
It looks like it could
go off-roading.
But at the same time,
it looks like a car
you could take
to a nice event.
You can dress it up
or dress it down.
This part's awesome.
Moderator:
The all-new Equinox comes
with built in 4G LTE Wi-Fi.
There's Wi-Fi?
Moderator:
Even a bird's-eye
surround vision camera.
Woman 4:
Wow, it shows
the view from up above?
How's it doing that?
(Laugh)
Boy:
I really like the sunroof.
Children:
What? Woah! Hello, world!
I feel like I'm only
saying good things.
Which is annoying.
(Laughter)
Moderator:
And all it takes to open
the Chevy Equinox liftgate
is the motion of your foot.
(Laughter)
Easy peasy.
I could definitely
get a lot in there.
I could put my entire
band's equipment...
Various:
Snowboard. Surfboards.
Mountain bike.
Even a sousaphone
would fit in there.
Yeah.
What's a sousaphone?
(Laughter)
Seems like the perfect
car for anybody.
I would take
it anywhere.
I want one.
I love it.
She's a bad mama-jama.
(Laughter)
Man 4:
Chevy stepped their game up.
Introducing McDonald's new
Signature Crafted Recipes.
(Laughter)
Like the Sweet Barbecue Bacon
sandwich.
Tangy barbecue sauce made with
sweet onions.
Thick cut Applewood smoked
bacon.
And topped with crispy, golden
onions.
On chicken or seared beef.
Need a fast absorbing
moisturizer?
Try NIVEA In-Shower body lotion.
Wash.
Apply. It absorbs fast.
For 24 hour moisture.
Quickly rinse for smoother skin.
Ready to go!
NIVEA In-Shower Body Lotion.
Also available with
Cocoa Butter.
♪ ♪ ♪
TAKING A CHANCE IS TOUGH.
WASHING COTTON IS EASY.
OH LIECHTENSTEIN...
IT'S L-I-C-T-H,
NO L-I-T-C-H, L-I-C-T?
OK GOOGLE,
HOW DO YOU SPELL LIECHTENSTEIN?
LIECHTENSTEIN IS SPELLED:
L-I-E-C-H-
YEAH THAT'S WHAT I MEANT.
In my experience there are only
two things guaranteed to grow,
the cash value of your
New York Life policy,
a policy that keeps
your family protected.
And my famous Crenn Soufflé,
which literally
never stops growing.
Be good at life.
New York Life.
Quin was crazy about curls.
But it took a twist of fate
to find a high-end curler
at such a head turning price.
And that's the beauty of
a store full of surprises.
You never know what
you're gonna find,
but you know
you're gonna love it.
♪
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!!!!!
Tom?
SNICKERS® Satisfies.
So, and you're sure
it's her?
It's her.
The Army won't tell you
unless they're certain.
And when is she coming?
Now. Tomorrow.
Does Nathan know?
No. Owen hasn't even told
his mom,
so, no,
Nathan doesn't know yet.
I'll tell him.
Well, if he's coming over,
just wait.
No. If Derek were alive,
I would want to know
right now.
Can you watch...
Yeah.
Okay, Ellis
needs her stuffie.
Story and bed by 8:00.
Yeah.
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Police radio chatter ]
-Have they found him yet?
-No.
And no word from Edwards?
No, and I can't
go looking for her.
I'm stuck here.
[ Sighs ]
Sit down.
Look.
There are cops everywhere.
They'll find her.
I know. I just...
I left her
in the room with him.
[ Beep at door ]
[ Police radio chatter ]
You know...
he probably got out
before they even called
the lockdown,
or they would've found him.
He's long gone.
Well, if that's true,
then why isn't she answering
her texts?
Maybe it's locked on
the other side of a door
from where she is.
I can't get to my phone
right now.
Yeah. Maybe so.
I mean, maybe.
Hey, she's okay.
Edwards is fine, all right?
She's fine.
You're not cynical.
I'm not cynical enough.
I was actually rooting
for them.
You made up a good story
about a patient.
Every one of us
has done that.
I liked your version a hell of
a lot better than the real one.
♪
[ Grunting ]
Why is he so mad?
[ Thumping on door ]
He's, uh,
having a bad day.
-[ Grunts ]
-Let's just stay quiet, okay?
I wanna go to my mom.
I want my mom and dad.
Ugh! There's gotta be
a way out of here!
There's got to be a way
to open it!
There isn't,
or I would've tried.
You open the door
right now!
I can't, okay?
I can't!
Nothing
is gonna open those doors
except security
calling off the lockdown.
Or -- Or, like,
emergency services.
W-What --
What do you mean?
It's like -- like a fire.
A fire or something.
[ Breathing quickly ]
♪
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on!
♪
Give me something
that I can start a fire with.
No. No! You can't.
You're not --
You can't start a fire in here!
Shut up, okay?
I'm just gonna set off
the sprinklers.
Make the doors open.
There'll be an evacuation.
Now, what can I use?
No, that's crazy.
You're gonna kill us all.
Erin: Will this work?
[ Breathes sharply ]
Will this make a fire?
[ Breathing quickly ]
You're a good girl.
♪
You got it. Atta girl.
Bring it here.
Set it on the floor
right there.
Stop it. Stop it.
Now, go in there and get
one of those blue things.
Stop making her help you.
You can help me.
And I can stand here with her.
Either way.
Now -- Now, squirt that stuff
all over the blue thing.
Don't do it. Don't do it, Erin!
Don't do it. Don't --
She's not
starting a fire for you.
Dammit!
Don't do it.
Come here. Come here.
-Come here.
-Come to me.
Hey, hey, hey.
You -- You stay right there.
Right there.
You stay right there.
♪
I don't like him.
Stephanie: It's okay.
He's gonna go soon.
[ Grunting ]
[ Sighs ]
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Now, when the doors unlock,
I'm gonna take your card
and the girl...
No! No, no.
Nobody's gonna stop a guy
carrying a kid
out of a burning building.
No, she stays with me.
[ Chuckling ]
No, you stay here.
Someone will find you
at some point.
[ Sparker clicking ]
[ Grunting ]
♪
Okay, Erin.
My name is Stephanie.
I want you to do me a favor.
Okay?
I just want you to turn around
and cover your eyes.
Okay.
Like hide and seek.
Okay, turn around.
Keep them covered.
Meredith: There are days
when you feel like
you can conquer anything.
[ Spker clicking ]
Keith: [ Grunting ]
♪
[ Fire ignites ]
Yeah, yes.
[ Chuckling ] Yes!
Come on.
Come on!
[ Breathing quickly ]
Come on. Come on.
[ Breathing heavily ]
♪
And it feels like everything
will be okay.
[ Breathing quickly ]
♪
[ Fire crackles ]
[ Screaming ]
♪
[ Panting ]
[ Groaning ]
Li I told you,
the feeling doesn't last.
I'm not trying to be cynical.
It's just that, even when
a day starts out so, so well...
Keith: [ Groaning ]
[ Breathing quickly ]
Oh, it's okay. It's okay.
You're okay, all right?
You're okay. We're okay.
[ Sniffling ]
We're gonna go.
I'm gonna take you
to see your parents.
It's okay.
[ Groaning continues ]
[ Groaning stops ]
♪
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
What is it?
Go. Go all the way
over there, okay?
Stay over there!
No! Stephanie.
I'll be right back, okay?
...that day can end...
[ Door opens ]
♪
[ Explosion, glass shattering ]
[ All gasping ]
[ Explosions ]
...so, so badly.
[ Curtis Mayfield's
"Move On Up" plays ]
I can confirm that, yes,
as of early this morning,
United States forces
have successfully dismantled
all the remaining drones.
[ Reporters clamoring ]
Carol.
Carol: What about
the people responsible?
Unfortunately,
I'm unable to tell you
anything more at this time.
The important thing
to remember here, folks,
is that the threat
is now gone.
Are there
any more questions?
[ All speaking indistinctly ]
With all this behind him,
what will President Grant
be focusing on
in his final days
of office?
The President
will continue to be
both passionate and eager,
Carol,
with a long list of interests
he still hopes to tackle.
♪ Toward your destination ♪
[ Both breathing heavily ]
♪ Though you may find
from time to time ♪
[ Laughs ]
♪ Complication ♪
Marcus:
The transition of power
will be both successful
and easy,
not just
for the President-Elect,
but for the country
as well.
Today, Americans
should be feeling excited
about what lies ahead,
invigorated
by the promises of tomorrow.
Well...
[Exhales deeply]
...what do you think?
I think you
should have told me
what a maid of honor
has to do.
Well, is it too much?
Not enough?
♪ Bite your lip ♪
No.
You look beautiful.
♪ And take a trip ♪
Now, I don't have
too many more chances
to stand up here in front of
all you lovely people,
and, well,
avoid your questions.
[ Laughter ]
♪ Just move on up ♪
But, I, for one,
am more optimistic
about this country's future
now more than ever.
We may just have another
week-and-a-half left here,
but we are not done.
We're not even close
to being done.
♪ So hush now, child ♪
Nine more days
left of this.
Nine more days.
♪ And don't you cry ♪
[ Laughs ]
Trust me, people,
when we're finished...
♪ Your folks
might understand you ♪
...you'll know.
♪ By and by ♪
[ Both exhale sharply ]
[ Laughs ]
♪ Move on up ♪
-- Captions by VITAC --
Captioning provided by
ABC Studios and ABC, Inc.
and brought to you by Ford.
We go further, so you can.
[ Door opens ]
Rowan:
Mr. Rosen, of all the people
I expected to see me off,
you were not on the list.
You're leaving?
I am.
Retiring.
My work here
is finally done.
[ Chuckles ]
At long last.
She is headed off
to the American Museum
of Natural History,
and I am heading off
to white sand beaches,
crystal-blue water.
I trust
you are not here
to try to keep that
from happening.
No. No, no, no.
Good.
Because the assassination of
Frankie Vargas
is a closed case,
is it not?
It is, yes. Absolutely.
No, I'm not here
in any official capacity.
Ah.
I'm here...
Well, I'm here
to ask about Samantha,
the mean one
with the ponytail.
She and I, we were --
Yes. I know.
I've been trying to figure out
what her real name is.
She gave me another one
during the interrogation --
Grace Dennis --
but it was another dead end.
She ever
say anything to you,
leave anything behind
that might help me
identify her?
A credit-card receipt?
Mnh-mnh.
She had a toothbrush
in my bathroom, red.
I threw it away.
Now I wish
I had kept it.
I could run her DNA
through the system,
identify her that way.
Or perhaps, Mr. Rosen,
it's time to move on?
If you knew
how it felt to be used,
someone
pretends to love you
and then uses you to try
to torpedo democracy...
But you're
leaving on a trip,
and I'm taking up
your time.
Safe travels.
Wait.
I, um...
I may have something
that could help.
♪
These all pardon petitions?
Fitz: Uh-huh.
I need to choose
which convicted prisoners
to pardon
by the end of the week.
You know you have
dozens of people
to sort through these
for you.
I'm being thorough --
hands on.
[ Giggles ]
You're being irresponsible,
because you're scared.
Scared? Of what?
Of Abby.
Of trusting Abby.
[ Papers fall on table ]
I want this done right.
Hmm.
You need to talk to her,
Fitz.
Have the difficult
conversation.
Either you let her back in
or you let her go.
Don't you have another President
to challenge and annoy?
I do.
Mm.
[ Door closes ]
♪
[ Camera shutter clicking ]
Abby: Today's schedule --
You've got Marcus at 11:00.
He'll prep you
for the BNC interview,
tell you what kind of questions
you're likely to be asked.
Then at 2:00 we've got Ackerman
coming over for pardons.
His aide gave me a heads up
last night
about which petitions
he'll be pushing.
I could stay --
tell you which ones
I'd recommend.
It's being taken care of.
Why don't you take
the rest of the day
and work from home?
Everything's good here.